Venkata Krishna

□ krishnagandla1415@gmail.com

+918886551234

im linkedin.com/in/venkata-krishna-gandla-6733785a/



SUMMARY

Passionate Sales & Marketing professional with valuable experience in Traditional and Digital Marketing. Excellent at combining advertising with promotional deals to enhance buyer incentives. Committed to working with marketing and sales departments to create enticing promotions.



EXPERIENCE

Sr Vice president

Runo Nov 2021 - Dec 2021

Develop and execute sales and go-to-market strategies as per AOP. Create operational plans for executing projects to achieve the maximum potential of the team. Control & monitor business performance adherence. Actively engaging with industry leaders and driving acquisition strategies across multiple locations and geographies.

AVP

OYO Mar 2017 - Oct 2021

Devising digital marketing strategies that have elevated brands from relative obscurity and driving revenue and growing profits in competitive markets. Lead long range marketing strategy, investment planning and initiatives to build brand health, optimize traffic and drive new customer acquisition. Responsible for driving content salience via SEO, Social and Organic efforts via competitive bench-marking, guest post blogging, building reputable back-links, social bookmarking and organization's blog content creation flow.

General Manager

Franchise India Jan 2014 - Mar 2017

Own the responsibility of delivering customers via all forms of paid digital spends (spends INR 8 Cr/Qtr), social media, SEO, organic and affiliate marketing efforts. Leveraged leadership in developing robust global digital marketing team with internal teams connects. Successfully enhanced customer acquisition (250%), activation (20%) and retention (20%) in less than a year.

Senior Manager

Thomas cook Nov 2007 - Dec 2013

Build and sustain strong corporate brand visibility, reputation and oversee corporate branding on all platforms. Develop and implement creative public relations/communications initiatives to deliver engaging and influential campaigns utilizing both traditional, social and digital media. Devising marketing strategies that elevated brands from relative obscurity and drove revenue and growing profits.



SKILLS

Go- to -Market strategy	• • • • •
Social Media	
Social Media	
CRM	
CRO and A/B Testing (optimized sign-up rates by 37%)	
SEO (grew organic traffic by 78% in 12 months)	••••
Strategy development	• • • • •
Lifecycle management	••••



CERTIFICATIONS

Certificate In Digital Marketing

Google Analytics certificate

Certificate in Social Media Marketing



EDUCATION

Masters of Business Administration

Jul 2004 - May 2006

Pondicherry University

Bachelor of Commerce & Computers

May 2001 - Apr 2004

Nagarjuna University